https://drrobpennington.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Please review our privacy policy below
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.drrobpennington.com. The statement does not apply to our practices on other Web sites or offline.
Choice/Opt-Out
If we send you an email, it will contain an opt-out link, which you can click to have your name removed from our e-mail list. We will not provide your name to third parties for any purpose. If your personally identifiable information changes, you can update it by contacting us by postal mail or email. You can also request to remove your information from our database using one of the following methods so you will not receive future communications or will no longer receive our service. Please allow up to 90 days for processing.
Send us a letter or email:
Dr. Rob Pennington, 6119 Bankside Drive, Houston, TX. 77096, or email at info@drrobpennington.com.
What Do We Collect and Why?
You may browse our site without providing us any information that is identifiable for you.
IP Address
We use your IP address and other standard log file information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address and other standard log information are used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information in the interest of improving our site and service.
Cookies and Click Trail Information
Our site uses cookies for a number of reasons, such as (a) to keep track of your shopping cart, (b) to recognize you when you return to our site and (c) to recognize whether a customer came to our site as a result of a promotion on one of our partners’ sites. Some of these cookies may be placed by our third party service providers to recognize when a user visits this site. The information collected and shared through this technology is non-personally identifiable. We also collect anonymous visitor information about how you utilize our site, such as IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer or Netscape), referring pages and pages visited. We use this information (a) to perform anonymous statistical analysis of Web page traffic patterns, (b) to administer our Web site and servers, and (c) to improve our services.
Registration Form
Registration forms on our site may require you to give us your contact information (i.e., name and e-mail address) and demographic information (i.e., zip code and state). We use this contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company at your request. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary for additional information or to process or fulfill your request. Demographic and profile data may also be collected. We use this data to help us improve this Web site and our product and service offerings.
Order Form
Our site uses an order form for you to request information, products, and services. We collect your contact information (i.e., e-mail address), financial information (i.e., credit card numbers), and demographic information (i.e., zip code and state). We use this contact information from the order form to send you a confirmation e-mail for which you cannot opt out. We also use this information to send you your orders, as well as information about our company and products and special promotions. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary for additional information to process or fulfill your order. Financial information that is collected is used to bill for products and services. Financial information is not retained or stored as part of your shopping profile, so you must enter your credit card number each time you place an order. Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to help us improve our Web site and our product and service offerings.
Surveys and Sweepstakes/Contests
From time to time, we may conduct online surveys to help us better understand and serve your needs, or conduct sweepstakes or contests. These offers may ask for contact information (i.e., e-mail address), financial information (i.e., credit card numbers), and demographic information (i.e., zip code, age, or income level). We may use this contact data from our surveys to send you information about our company. Unique identifiers are collected from the Web site to verify your identity. We use this data to help us improve our Web site and our product and service offerings.
Information from Other Sources
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (i.e., providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.
Links to Other Sites
This site contains links to other sites. www.drrobpennington.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Revisions to this Statement
Our business changes constantly. This privacy statement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy and security statement in effect at the time of collection. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.
If you have any questions about this privacy and security statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us using one of the methods above.
